Guide to the Wiltwyck School for Boys records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Executive Director Files, 1942-1981
  - Subseries 2: Subject Files, 1965-1981
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus
      - Neighbors, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 361)
      - Night Counselor Staff Meetings, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 362)
      - Procedures--General, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 363)
      - Recreation/Vocational Program, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 364)
      - Reorganization Plans, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 365)
      - Rooms/Apartments, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 366)
      - Special Report, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 367)
      - Vocational Training Program, undated (Box 18, Folder 368)
      - Westchester Friends of Wiltwyck, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 369)
    - Evaluations, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 370)
    - Evaluations--Brooklyn Student Unit, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 371)
    - Evaluations--Brooklyn--Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 372)
      [restricted until 2056]
    - Executive Cabinet, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 373)
    - Executive Director Files, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 374-376)
      [restricted until 2050]
    - Family, Conference on the, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 377)
    - Family Project undated (Box 18, Folder 378)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1972-1981, (6 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 379-384)
      - Division on Child and Family Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 385)
      - Harlem Agencies for Neighborhood Development, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder F.386)
      - Juvenile Justice Project, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 387)
      - Task Force, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 388)
    - Final Evaluations, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 389)
    - Finance, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 390)
    - Financial Memoranda, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 391)
    - Financial Statements, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 392)
    - Fiscal Department, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 393)
    - Fiscal Department--Save Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Campaign, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - Fiscal Operating Statement, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - Floyd Patterson House--Therapist and Counselor Summaries, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 396)
      [restricted until 2048]
    - Food Service Department, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - Fordham-Tremont Community Mental Health Center, 1978-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 398-399)
    - Fordham University, 1970-1979, (3 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 400-402)
    - Foster Care, 1974-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 403-404)
    - Foster Grandparent Program, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 405)
    - Foundations, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 406)
    - Fundraising, 1970-1974, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 407-408)
    - Fundraising Department, 1974-1976, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 409-410)
    - Fundraising and Public Relations, 1976-1981, (6 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 411-416)
    - Fundraising and Public Relations--Press Releases, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 417)
    - Fundraising and Public Relations--Procedures and Form Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 418)
    - Furnishings, 1973-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 419-420)
    - George Junior Republic Association, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 421)
    - Governor's Panel on Juvenile Violence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 422)
    - Grants, 1974-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 423-425)
    - Grant Request, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 426)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1970-1981, (8 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 427-434)
    - Grievance Material--Union, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 435)
      [restricted until 2057]
    - Group Homes, 1970-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 436-437)
    - Group Homes, 1974-1979, (5 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 438-442)
      [restricted until 2059]
    - Group Home C, 1975-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 443-444)
    - Group Home D, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 445)
    - Group Home D, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 446)
    - Group Home D Lawsuit, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 447)
    - Group Home Hartsdale, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 448)
    - Group Home Proposal, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 449)
    - Group Life, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 450-451)
    - Harlem Catchment Area, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 452-453)
    - Harlem Catchment Planning Group, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 454)
    - Harlem Neighborhood Association, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 455)
    - Harris, Kenneth, undated (Box 21, Folder 456)
    - Havens Relief Fund Society, 1972-1981, (6 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 457-462)
    - Hearings and Interviews, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 463)
    - Hellman, Martin, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 464)
    - Homemaker/Organizer, undated (Box 21, Folder 465)
    - Homemaker, Organizer, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 466)
    - Human Ecology Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 467)
    - Hunter College, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 468)
    - Insurance Matters, 1974-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 469-470)
    - Intakes, 1972-1976, (6 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 471-476)
      [1974 Folder is restricted until 2054]
    - Intake Policy, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 477)
    - Inter-agency Council on Child Welfare, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 478)
    - Inter-disciplinary Generic Training Program, 1972-1979, (11 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 479-489)
      - Committee, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 490)
      - Student Evaluations, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 491)
    - Interiors, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 492)
    - Inventory of Books, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 493)
    - Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 494)
    - Jewish Board of Guardians, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 495)
    - Job Descriptions, 1971-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 496-497)
    - Jobs '70 Program, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 498)
    - Joint Action for Children, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 499)
    - Key to Abbreviations, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 500)
    - King, Roy, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 501)
    - Landau, Martin, undated (Box 23, Folder 502)
    - Lawsuits, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 503)
    - Lawsuit--Child v. Beame, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 504)
    - Lawsuits--Wilder/Sugarman, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 505-506)
    - Lease, undated (Box 23, Folder 507)
    - Lease Amendment to Union Free School District, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 508)
    - Lease Information, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 509)
    - Legal Aid Society, 1973-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 510-511)
    - Legislation, 1974-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 512-514)
    - Legislation, 1978-1981, (4 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 515-518)
      - Social Welfare, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 519)
      - Title XX, 1974-1976, (3 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 520-522)
    - Library, 1974-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 523-534)
      - Clinical and Research Building, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 535)
      - Procedures, undated (Box 24, Folder 536)
    - Litigation, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 537)
    - Lloyd, Edward, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 538)
    - Manhattan Center, 1973-1980, (6 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 539-544)
    - Manhattan Unit, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 545-547)
    - Manual of Job Descriptions, undated (Box 24, Folder 548)
    - Mashikian, Hagop S., 1967 (Box 24, Folder 549)
    - Mayor's Advisory Council on Juvenile Institutions, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 550)
    - Medical Department, 1971-1978, (5 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 551-555)
    - Meetings
      - Administrative Staff, 1970-1973, (4 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 556-559)
      - All-Agency Supervisors, 1971-1975, (5 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 559-563)
      - Boys' Council, l973-1978, (4 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 564-567)
      - Cabinet, 1970-1975, (6 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 568-573)
      - Conference, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 574)
      - Executive Staff, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 575)
      - In-Service Training, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 576)
      - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 577)
      - Residential Operations Committee, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 578)
      - Review Conferences, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 579)
      - School Board, 1971-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 580-581)
      - Supervisors, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 582)
      - Team, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 583)
      - Training Sessions for Community Center Staff, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 584)
      - Volunteer Department, undated (Box 25, Folder 585)
    - Memos
      - Clinical Staff, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 586)
      - Rosmini and Volunteers, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 587)
    - Mennonite Central Committee, 1971-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 588-589)
    - Mental Health
      - 1973 (Box 25, Folder 590)
      - Brooklyn Association for, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 591)
      - Coalition, 1974-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 592-593)
      - Coalition of Voluntary Mental Health and Mental Retardation Contract Agencies, 1976-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 594-596)
      - Westchester Association for, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 597)
    - Metropolitan Applied Research Center, undated (Box 25, Folder 598)
    - Minutes, Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Committee, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 599)
    - Musical Psychology Program, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 600)
    - Nassau County, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 601)
    - National Association of Black Social Workers, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 602)
    - National Association of Social Workers, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 603)
    - National Institute of Mental Health, 1967-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 604-605)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 606)
    - National Conference on Social Welfare, 1974-1976, (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 607-608)
    - National Conference on Social Work, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 609)
    - National Urban League, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 610)
    - National Youth Service, 1978-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 611-612)
    - New Muse, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 613)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1971-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 614-615)
      (Clippings in Oversize Box)
    - New York City
      - 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 616)
      - Addiction Services Agency, 1970-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 617-619)
      - Board of Social Welfare, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 620)
      - Bureau of Labor Services, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 621)
      - Coalition for Juvenile Justice and Youth Services, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 622)
      - Community Mental Health Board, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 623)
      - Criminal Justice Coordinating Council, 1974-1977, (4 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 624-626)
      - Criminal Justice Coordinating Council, 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 627)
      - Department of Mental Health and Mental Retardation Services, 1970-1981, (10 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 628-637)
        - Alcoholism Services, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 638-639)
        - Alcoholism Services, 1979-1980 (Box 28)
        - Information Notice, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 640)
        - Manhattan Regional Federation of Mental Health and Mental Retardation Agencies--Children's Services Committee, 1975-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 641-643)
        - Manhattan Regional Federation, Harlem Catchment Area, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 644)
      - Department of Social Services, 1971-1981, (9 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 645-653)
      - Department of Social Welfare, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 654)
      - Division--Minutes, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 655)
      - Housing Authority, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 656)
      - Human Resources Administration, 1977-1981, (5 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 657-661)
        - Homemaker Services, 1976-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 662-663)
        - Homemaker Services, 1977-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 664-665)
        - Inter-agency Manual, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 666)
        - Inter-agency Planning Committee, 1976-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 667-668)
        - Procedures and Bulletins, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 669)
        - Special Services for Children, 1973-1975, (5 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 670-674)
        - Special Services for Children, 1976-1980, (8 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 673-677)
          (1977 and 1978 Folder)
        - Procedures and Bulletins, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 683)
      - Mission Society, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 684)
      - Task Force on the New York City Crisis, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 685)
      - Task Force on the New York City Crisis, 1976-1979, (4 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 686-689)
        - Foster Care Services, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 690)
        - Subcommittee on Mental Health, 1976-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 691-692)
      - Youth Board, 1976-1980, (5 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 693-697)
        - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 698)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 699)
    - New York Council on Adoptable Children, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 700)
    - New York Insurance Compensation Board, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 701)
    - New York Office, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 702)
    - New York State
      - Association for Human Services, 1975-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 703-705)
      - Association for Mental Health Program Committee, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 706)
      - Board of Social Welfare, 1973-1977, (4 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 707-710)
      - Board of Social Welfare, 1977-1979, (3 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 711-713)
      - Coalition for Juvenile Justice and Youth Services, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 714)
      - Community Mental Health Services Act, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 715)
      - Council of Voluntary Child Care Agencies, 1970-1981, (88 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 716-723)
      - Department of Mental Health, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 724)
      - Department of Mental Hygiene, 1965-1972, (3 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 725-727)
      - Department of Mental Hygiene, 1965-1978, (5 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 728-732)
        - Out-Patient Clinic, 1965-1969, (2 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 733-734)
        - Out-Patient Psychiatric Facility, 1971-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 735-737)
        - Proposal, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 738)
        - Proposal Follow-up, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 739)
      - Department of Social Services, 1968-1980, (10 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 740-749)
        - Council on Child Welfare, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 750)
        - Investigation, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 751)
      - Department of Social Welfare Application, 1965, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 752-753)
      - Division of Criminal Justice Services, 1976-1979, (4 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 754-757)
        - Committee on Emergency Preparedness, 1977-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 758-759)
        - Crime Control Planning Board, 1976-1978, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 760-761)
      - Division for Youth, 1975-1980, (4 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 762-765)
      - Drug Abuse Control Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 766)
      - Education Department, 1970-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 767-768)
      - Governor's Panel on Juvenile Justice, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 769)
      - Juvenile Justice Advisory Board, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 770)
      - Northwest Regional Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 771)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 772)
      - Office of Mental Health, 1978-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 773-774)
      - Office of Mental Hygiene--Special Services for Children, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 775)
      - Oral Examinations for Civil Service, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 776)
      - State Communities Aid Association, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 777)
      - Welfare Conference, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 778)
    - Organization, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 779)
    - Other Agencies, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 780)
    - Out-Patient Clinic, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 781)
      - Memoranda, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 782)
      - Statistical Reports, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 783)
    - Paramount Releases, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 784)
    - Parents' Association, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 785)
    - Parsons, Brinkerhoff, Quade, and Douglas, Inc. 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 786)
    - Patient Profiles, 1960-1974, (4 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 787-790)
    - Patterson House
      - Admission Policy, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 791)
      - Administrative Meetings, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 792)
      - Annotated Bibliography, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 793)
      - Budget, Program Proposal, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 794)
      - Christmas Plans and Programs, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 795)
      - Cole, Gary, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 796)
      - Duncan, Dave, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 797)
      - Educational Supervisor, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 798)
      - Evolution of a Group Counselor, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 799)
      - Family Therapy Seminar, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 800)
      - Film Proposal, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 801)
      - Fochios, Dr. Steve, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 802)
      - Morrison, Jay, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 803)
      - Myers, Edward, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 804)
      - News, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 805)
      - Preiskel, Mrs. Robert H., 1967 (Box 36, Folder 806)
    - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton, Garrison, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 807)
    - Personnel
      - General, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 808-809)
      - Applications, 1979-1981 (Box 36, Folder 810)
        [restricted until 2061]
      - Dale, Nan, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 811)
      - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 812)
      - Fireman, Barry I., 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 813)
      - Former Staff, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 814)
      - Holding, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 815)
      - Job Descriptions, 1971-1981, (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 816-817)
      - Manual, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 818)
      - Poole, Robert, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 819)
      - References, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 820)
      - Salaries, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 821)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 822)
    - Policy Statement, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 823)
    - Population, 1976-1981, (5Folders) (Box 36, Folder 824-828)
      - Follow-up Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 829)
    - Procedures, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 830-831)
      - Intake, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 832)
      - Personnel and Policy, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 833)
    - Programs, 1969-1971, (2 Folders) (Box 37, Folder 834-835)
      - Descriptions and Bibliographies, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 836)
      - Development, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 837)
      - Guidelines, undated (Box 37, Folder 838)
    - Projects, undated, 1969-1971, (2 Folders) (Box 37, Folder 839-840)
      - Demonstration, undated (Box 37, Folder 841)
      - Follow-up Evaluation, undated (Box 37, Folder 842)
      - To be Reviewed, undated (Box 37, Folder 843)
    - Proposals, 1974-1978, (5 Folders) (Box 37, Folder 844-888)
      - Bedford-Stuyvesant, undated (Box 37, Folder 889)
      - Central Brooklyn Community Care, undated (Box 37, Folder 890)
      - Comprehensive, undated (Box 37, Folder 891)
      - Division of Criminal Justice Services, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 892)
      - Reorganization, 1964-1967, (3 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 893-895)
      - Research and Demonstration Project, undated (Box 38, Folder 896)
      - Studies of Families and Children in Residential Treatment, 1962, (6 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 897-902)
    - Psychiatric Evaluations, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 903)
    - Psychiatric Services, 1973-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 38, Folder 904-906)
    - Psychiatric Staff, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Psychology Certification Law, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 907)
    - Publications, 1966-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 908-910)
    - Publicity, 1970-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 911-912)
    - Public Relations, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 913-914)
    - Putnam, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 915)
    - Rationale--Overall Organization and Program, undated (Box 39, Folder 916)
    - Real Estate, 1974-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 917-919)
      - Bronx, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 920)
      - Brooklyn, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 921)
      - Brooklyn--Brownsville, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 922)
      - Manhattan, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 923)
    - Record-Keeping Survey, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 924)
    - Recruitment of Counselors, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 925)
    - Recreation Department, 1971-1975 undated, (5 Folders) (Box 39, Folder 926-930)
    - Reference Material, undated (Box 39, Folder 931)
    - Rehabilitation of Transgenerationally Deprived and Dependent Families, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 932)
    - Reports, 1971-1978, (5 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 933-937)
      [1977 Folder restricted until 2057]
      - Personnel--Wiltwyck Experience, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 938)
      - Quiet Room, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 939)
    - Requests for Information, 1973-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 940-942)
    - Research, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 943)
    - Research--Eleanor Roosevelt Campus Crime, 1980-1971 (Box 40, Folder 944)
    - Research, Training, and Program Development, 1974-1977, (3 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 945-947)
    - Residential Programs, 1977, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 948-949)
    - Rockland County, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 950)
    - Rotary Club Project, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 951)
    - Rough Draft, Research Plan, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 952)
    - Saving Families for Children, 1975-1977, (2 Folders) (Box 40, Folder 953-954)
    - Schools of Social Work, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 955)
    - Schwerner Memorial Fund, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 956)
    - Silcott, T. George, 1969-1973 (Box 40, Folder 957)
    - Social Service, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 958)
      - Department, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 959)
    - Social Work Material, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 960)
    - Statistics--Comparative Re-treatment, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 961)
    - Staff Retreats, 1971, (2 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 962-963)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 964)
    - Stenographic Manual, undated (Box 41, Folder 965)
    - Strike, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 966)
    - Structure, Functions, and Operations, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 967)
    - Students in Placement, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 968)
    - Suffolk County, 1979-1981, (2 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 969-970)
    - Summer Program, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 971)
      - Eleanor Roosevelt Campus, Brooklyn, Bronx, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 972)
    - Taconic Foundation, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 973)
    - Teacher Training, Mercy College, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 974)
    - Title I, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 975)
    - Title III, Elementary and Secondary Act of 1965, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 976)
    - Training, 1969-1980, (7 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 977-983)
      - Child Care Staff, undated (Box 41, Folder 984)
      - Material, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 985)
        [restricted until 2045]
      - Sessions, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 986)
    - Treatment Approach, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 987)
    - Treatment Committee, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 988)
    - Union, 1969-1980, (6 Folders) (Box 41, Folder 989-994)
    - Union Contract, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 995)
    - United Fund of Greater New York, 1974-1976, (3 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 996-998)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 999)
    - United States General, 1979-1980 (Box 42, Folder 1000)
      - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1971-1979, (8 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 1001-1008)
      - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), 1978-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 42, Folder 1009-1010)
    - United Way of Tri-State, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 1011)
    - Urban Home Ownership Program, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1012)
    - Urban League, National, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 1013)
      - United States--Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 42)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, 1977-1978 (Box 42)
      - Vera Institute of Justice, 1977-1978 (Box 43)
      - Virgin Islands, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1014)
      - Vista Program, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 1015)
      - Vocational Services, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 1016)
      - Volunteers, 1973-1978, (4 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 1017-1020)
      - Volunteer Opportunities, Inc., 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1021)
      - Weiner, Howard A., 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1022)
      - Welfare Information, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 1023)
      - Welfare Research Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 43)
      - Westchester (Box 43, Folder 1024)
        - Community Opportunity Program, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 1025)
        - Council of Social Agencies, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 1026)
        - County, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 1027)
          - Department of Health,1978-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 1028-1029)